virginiabeach.com 2019-12-12

# VirginiaBeach.com Privacy Policy | Virginia Beach

VirginiaBeach.com, Inc. (we) has published this privacy policy to better serve those interested in knowing how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used on this [www.virginiabeachcom](http://www.virginiabeachcom/) (website). PII, as noted in US privacy law, is any information that can be used on its own to identify, locate, or contact a single person or identify an individual in context. This privacy policy will give you a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect, and/or handle your PII, if applicable.

### Personal information collected on website

When registering to use our website (not required for reading) or when ordering products, you may be asked for your name, email and mailing address, phone number, and other details to complete your registration or order.

### When if PII collected?

We collect and store PII when you place an order, register to post content, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, or request information from us.

### How is this information used?

We may use your information to complete your registration, complete and ship any purchased items, send requested periodic newsletters, respond to your submitted poll / user survey / submitted question, or allow you access to post content to our website.

### Protecting your PII

Our website is monitored and scanned regularly to look for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make any stored information as secure as possible. 

We also use regular Malware Scanning.

All PII is stored behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of people who have special access and are under confidentiality agreements. In addition, all interaction with the website is protected by SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology.

All PII is protected when orders are placed and no credit card information is stored locally on the website. All CC transactions are processed through a secure, third-party gateway provider (PayPal); not on the website.

### Are Cookies Used

Yes. Cookies are tiny bits of information stored in your web browser's cache or computer's hard drive. Most are unique to your username/activity. We use cookies to remember and process your orders and remember your access registration. They are also used to allow you to customize your access and user profile on our website. Cookies are also used with Google Analytics, to track user behavior on the website. This includes, but is not limited to, the amount of time spent on a page, bounce rates, and other website related metrics.

Cookies can be disabled by you in your web browser. If you disable cookies, some features may no longer function properly or as efficiently, although the majority of the website and features will work without significant impact.

### Third-party disclosure

VirginiaBeach.com, Inc. does not sell, trade, or transfer to outside parties any of your PII unless we provide you with advance notice. This doesn't include website hosting and sponsors who help us operate our website, as long as those parties agree to keep all information secure and confidential and spam-free. Information may also be released to comply with law enforcement, enforce site policy, or to protect our safety and rights and any others'.

However, non-personally identifiable information can be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. This is anonymous information and not specific to you as an individual.

### Third-party links

We may include links and offers to other websites or services on our website. Those external links will have a separate and independent privacy policy that will differ from ours. We do not have any responsibility or liability for the information, content, products, and activities of those external sites. However, we welcome your feedback to any linked site or content you may find on our website.

### Google

Google's Advertising Principles are used on this website and are intended to provide a positive experience. They can be found at the link below:

<https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

### Google AdSense Advertising

Google uses cookies to show ads on our website. You may opt-out by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. Google Analytics are also used on this website to track user interaction as they related to our website only.

### Do Not Track settings

We fully support Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is being utilized.

### Fair Information Practices

In our support of Fair Information Practices, VirginiaBeach.com will take the following responsive steps, should a breach of data be experienced:

We will post a site notification to all users within seven business days.

We also agree to and support the Individual Redress Principle. This gives individuals the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law and are non-compliant. 

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a US law that addresses potential abuse for commercial email, establishes needed requirements for commercial messages, gives individuals the right to stop unwanted emails, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

Our website collects email addresses in order to:

• Send information and responses to inquiries.  
• Process authorized orders and to send information and updates pertaining to said orders.  
• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service  
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

• Never use false or misleading subjects or e-mail content.  
• Properly identify the e-mail as an advertisement in a reasonable way.  
• Include the mailing address of our business.  
• Promptly honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests.  
• Allow users to unsubscribe, using the link at the bottom of each e-mail.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding our privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

VirginiaBeach.com, Inc.  
PO Box 2068  
Yorktown, VA 23692  
United States  

Last edited: April 21, 2017
